As he waits at a zebra crossing, a pristine red Camry pulls alongside.
The sight sparks memories of wild nights and fast cars with old friends.
At the school gates, his niece Charlotte bursts forth her joy infectious.
Uncle Jimmy, she exclaims, leaping into his arms.
Their bond is immediate and full of warmth.
Driving away, Charlotte chatters excitedly in the back seat,
her story's painting pictures of her day.
James listens, his heart swelling with love.
Their next stop is the quaint home of James's aging parents.
Inside, the air is filled with the comfortable familiarity of family love and
gentle care with grandparents, groceries and Charlotte in tow.
The family car is a scene of joyful chaos.
They play a guessing game, laughter filling the air.
Suddenly, the mood shatters.
A truck collides with their car, screams pierce the air,
metal crunches and in moments, lives change forever.
In the eerie silence that follows, James, dazed and injured,
tries to comprehend the devastation.
As he looks up, he sees the red Camry again.
It's driver now a witness to his deepest loss.