The sun rose over the sleepy town of Abeokuta, where Iyabo Oni began her first day as a teacher.
Dressed impeccably in a tailored skirt suit, her most noticeable accessory was a pair of
shiny red heels, a gift from her mother.
As she walked by, the sound of her heels, koi, koi, koi, koi, echoed, turning heads
and drawing whispers from students.
Her teaching style was strict.
Her methods, often called harsh, drew mixed reactions from her fellow teachers and students
alike.
The turning point in Iyabo's life occurred on a Tuesday afternoon when her fiancée,
Adeola, a lawyer from Lagos, appeared at the school.
Iyabo was summoned to the principal's office, where Adeola said he could not go through
with the marriage.
Iyabo's legs gave way as she fell in a mix of shock and despair.
The news of the broken engagement spread through the school like wildfire.
She felt the weight of every whisper and sideways glance from both students and teachers.
She began to perceive the laughter of students as mocking, and one day she could not take
it any longer.