The repercussions were immediate, and she was dismissed from her position.
Humiliated and enraged, she blamed the students for her downfall, vowing revenge against them.
On her journey back home, Iyabo was involved in a severe accident.
Her last moments were consumed by thoughts of vengeance and betrayal.
Her spirit, unable to find peace, became tied to the school where she felt her dreams had
been destroyed.
Not long after her death, students and teachers began to report strange and scary occurrences.
Doors would slam shut.
A single red heel was found in classrooms, and the unmistakable sound of her heels, koi,
koi, koi, koi, was heard through empty hallways at night.
The legend of Madam Koi Koi was born.